(audience clapping)
("I Want You Back")
♪ Uh-oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Let me tell you now ♪
♪ Uh-Huh, oh, oh,
ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ When I had you to myself ♪
♪ I didn't want you around ♪
♪ Those pretty faces
always made you ♪
♪ Stand out in a crowd ♪
♪ But someone picked
you from the bunch ♪
♪ One glance was all it took ♪
♪ Now it's much
too late for me ♪
♪ To take a second look ♪
♪ Oh, baby, give me
one more chance ♪
♪ To show you that I love you ♪
♪ Won't you please let me ♪
♪ Back in your heart ♪
♪ Oh, darling, I was
blind to let you go ♪
♪ Let you go baby ♪
♪ But now since I
see you in his arms ♪
♪ I want you back
- yes, I do now ♪
- ooh ooh, baby ♪
♪ I want you back -
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
now, now, now, now ♪
♪ Trying to live
without your love ♪
♪ Is one long sleepless night ♪
♪ Let me show you girl ♪
♪ That I know wrong from right ♪
♪ Every street you walk on ♪
♪ I leave tearstains
on the ground ♪
♪ Following the girl ♪
♪ I didn't even want around ♪
♪ Let me tell you now ♪
♪ Oh, baby, all I need
is one more chance ♪
♪ To show you that I love you ♪
♪ Won't you please let me ♪
♪ Back in your heart ♪
♪ Oh, darling, I was
blind to let you go ♪
♪ Let you go baby ♪
♪ But now since I
see you in his arms ♪
♪ Uh, huh ♪
♪ Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum ♪
♪ All I want, buh
bum, bum, bum ♪
♪ All I need, buh
♪ All I want, buh
bum, bum, bum ♪
♪ All I need ♪
♪ Oh, just one more chance to ♪
♪ show that I love you ♪
♪ Baby - Baby ♪
♪ Baby, baby, I want you back ♪
♪ Forget what happened then ♪
♪ And let me live again ♪
♪ Oh, darlin' I was
blind to let you go ♪
♪ But now since I see you in
his arms - I want you back ♪
♪ Spare me of this cost
(I want you back) ♪
♪ And give back what I lost ♪
♪ Oh darlin' I need
one more chance, hah! ♪
♪ I tell ya that I love you ♪
♪ Baby - Oh! - Baby
- Oh! - Baby - Oh! ♪
♪ I want you back ♪
(audience clapping)